Hi and welcome to this course.
My name is Maximilian Schwartz Miller and I will be your instructor in this course.
Now this course is about typescript superset 2 javascript.
So a programming language which actually builds up on javascript you could say it takes javascript to
the next level with typescript.
You will see in this course you can write less error prone much better and cleaner code and all use
some exciting new features which don't exist like this in javascript.
Now in this course you will learn typescript from scratch.
You don't need to know anything about TIBCO to get started.
Basic javascript knowledge absolutely suffices.
You will learn all the basics of typescript how it works why we use it the different advantages it offers.
We'll dive into the core types it provides and we'll gradually build up knowledge and dive into more
and more advanced typescript features for all at this course.
Now this course is both a course that focuses on the theory and showing a broad variety of features
as well as showing all these features in action in real projects.
Therefore in this course we'll have a real project.
We'll also have a module where we dive into typescript with react.
We'll also have a module where we dive into typescript with node and express sorted by the end of this
course.
You really feel comfortable using typescript in your next projects and then you know why you would use
it.
And most importantly how you would apply it to any javascript project you're working on.
No matter.
By the way if data is JavaScript in the browser with or without any framework or if it's on the service
side.
So that's all in the course.
I'm super excited to start this journey together with you and with that I'd say let's not waste any
time and let's find out what exactly types code is and which advantages it has to offer.